And there is a neighbor.
Hello!
- Where are you going?
Should you cut yourself?
Can you see the hairstyle now?
Can we meet you then when we pull and see how it became?
- Sure you get.
- Do you have any idea why we are here?
- Yes, then ...
No, maybe something to do with weightlifting?
- What are your biggest passions in life?
- I play a lot.
Fortnite is the best I know.
- What, you should become a professional?
- Yes, but that would have been the dream.
Sit and stream and work with.
So just play.
It would have been absolutely fantastic.
- But what stops you then?
- Yes, my computer has not been completely gallant.
- Why don't you buy a new one?
Like, come on.
Okay, now it's two hours earlier.
We stand here with Matti's best friend.
We have to fix some stuff for him today.
Because you have no super computer yourself, but you want to give him a good computer.
A real brother is what you are.
- Last Sunday night, then it was a tournament.
But then in the middle of the tournament, his computer crashed.
So then we could not continue.
- And now we will immediately go to the Elgiganten and fix a really bold gaming computer.
And he has no idea.
- No.
- He doesn't have a rush.
- It feels unreal.
Don't know if I dream.
- Let's go!
- It's like you just start nosy on the most expensive computer in the department.
What else do you want then?
Now that you're in such a greedy mood.
- A mouse, keyboard, screen, chair.
- Chair?
A chair?
- Yes, but that's good.
- So, if I'm here, where is Jocke and Jonna.
- So.
- Up there?
- It's a bit up to.
I have a bit left.
I think we should go away.
And then you should simply see what your surprise is.
- That's a good idea.
- Do you feel tagged?
- I'm peppered.
- You're peppered?
- Yes.
- Let's go.
- Should we pull.
- Now I have to put on an blindfold so you don't really know what's going on.
- Okay.
- Now you are getting nervous.
It's nothing dangerous.
- I'm not nervous.
- Do you promise it?
- One two Three.
- Hello.
- You can hug them.
- Do you get a hug?
Is it okey?
- It's funny.
- It is fun.
Now they stand here.
- Yes.
- You can hug them again if you want.
- Yes, I want that.
- We thought you could record a Youtube video with Jocke and Jonna today.
Isn't that good news anyway?
- Yes.
- Do you want to come in and look around a bit?
- We'll do that now.
- So fun!
- Here now at the elderly home in Linköping we have Maxida Märak.
One of Sweden's absolute best jokes.
You have traveled from Jokkmokk to surprise Brit.
- I was told that Stig had wanted this to Brit, to his grandmother.
- I myself have had many around me older who have also suffered from dementia.
Although she is now in a completely different world-
- So it is still a world that for her is very active.
Getting a part of it and maybe gilding it a little is huge for me.
This will be Brit's joke.
- Now comes the surprise.
- Hello!
- My name is Maxida Märak
It is incredible to be here.
And she hasn't had it easy.
- How is it as a daughter to see her mother in this situation?
Ehm ...
Very poor.
Ugh I will start crying.
I can't describe the feeling.
But we have no time to lose so we went down to central Kungälv to stage a small three-stage rocket-
-Hopefully can kick start the restaurant again.
- Now we are down in Kungälv, at your mother's restaurant.
I thought I would bring some extra guests.
What do you say?
It is still good for the day cash register.
- Delicious!
- No, but it was just good in general.
- It tasted delicious!
- So, ten out of ten.
- How much does this restaurant mean to you?
- How much would it mean to you if this restaurant began to flourish again-
-and you got a lot of new customers?
- Do you want to tell them that they are welcome here?
I can not!
- Oh, you hide here behind me.
And now it was time for step two in our three -stage rocket.
- What is the tone?
- What?
No, but it was good.
Unbelievable!
I thought it was good!?
Now there, after all, the question, can you with credibility post on your social media that this tastes good?
Yes!
1, 2, 3!
- We would just pull and then we met this man.
Can you tell us that you found out that you were going here today?
- I looked at Instagram.
We hurried here with the moped.
- Why do flowers make you so happy then?
- I do not know.
But before we gave the surprise ourselves, Malin attracted the folk high school where the education takes place.
With the lid that she should be able to create her own bouquet with a teacher.
Hello?
Hello Hello.
- Today Malin will only have an outlet for everything she loves.
- It smells good already.
- It's like a new person standing here.
This smile of being in this environment.
- You like to do flowers?
-It's the best I know.
Actually, I would like to work as a florist.
- What are we going to do here?
- No, you are joking?
- No, it's not a joke.
- Then was...
Yes, what fun.
Yes thank you very much.
What strange, can you hug you?
You have told me many times.
To do it just.
- Yes.
I feel that your life is too short to keep up with what you don't want.
- Yes, just right.
- You just sacrificed everything for us all our lives.
You are so worth here, so I just want you to do it now.
-In that she had a little difficulty.
So her dad recently went away.
It has not been so fun lately.
Then I want to raise her mood.
It is difficult what to do.
- What should we do to raise her mood?
- Give her a sea of yarn.
- We received so much mail.
People wanted travel.
You just, could we get some yarn?
Then I felt that here had to go.
She who wants yarn for her friend.
Why should we give all this yarn to Indra?
- She crochet and crochet and crochet.
I heard all the time that her fingers hurt.
Before Indra's dad died, she began to crochet on a blanket to him-
- If he would survive.
She never had it clear before he died.
- So she never got to give the blanket?
-How horrible.
-Yes.
- But God, I feel that Indra deserves all this yarn.
She should have this yarn.
- Here lives Indra.
Are you nervous?
- Giant!
Hello indra!
- We have a little thing for you.
-How are you?
-Good.
- It's good?
-Yes.
- Sanna told us about a great passion you have in life.
- We have fixed some yarn.
-Oh my God!
Oh my God!
Thanks so much.
It's so nice to get something that means so much.
It's totally sick.
- When you see all that, do I have to suggest a classic party of yarnwar?
I left this wonderful duo and continued to our last destination Luleå.
Here Samuel was waiting for me, who wanted to give his dad a working car over the summer.
So the father can do what he loves the most.
To go and meet their children who moved far from home.
- Why does your dad need a car over the summer?
- It is mainly to be able to go around Sweden and visit us children.
- You take the bus to work, right?
- Yes, it gets a little cheaper.
- What else do you like.
do then?
- I am very interested in sports.
It is very chatting in the chat group Spring when it is hockey.
You are in different places but you still have that in common.
- How much do you hang out with your children?
- Now it is difficult when they do not live in the city.
- You would have liked to meet them more often?
- Yes, you always want that.
They must have their lives.
- You can stay sometimes?
- Yes exactly.
- Are you starting to get annoying?
What kind of crap I boiled together?
- Yes, a little curious.
- Now we are approaching.
A little Patrik surprise.
- Yes, you are here too.
I'm a little nervous about what you've found.
This!
- Oh!
- What do you say about that?
A little gift from me and Volvo on Demand!
- Yes, what should I say?
I'm speechless.
It is superb!
It's worth so much.
Incredibly much.
Thank you very much.
Thanks.
- As a small extra-lights, you should also get 5,000 bucks in fuel.
Just so you can go.
- Thanks so much, I say.
It is absolutely incredible.
This I will remember incredibly long.
- Yes, you were going to say for the rest of your life, but you regretted the road and it was incredibly long.
Now you have your new car.
I still want to be involved when you inaugurate it.
Where should we go?
What can we think of?
- Coffee.
- Coffee?
- Now the summer begins.
- Now the summer begins!